A Guide to the John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, Audiovisual Materials, RG 7 FA1801
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Transparencies, 1970-2003; 7; 0.19 Cubic Feet 1 half-letter box
  - People, 1970-2003; 2; 0.07 Cubic Feet
    - People - Groups, 1987-2003; 2.2
      - Magic of Music Orchestra Initiative - Wichita Symphony, 2003 November 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
        Knight File Number - 3017
        Wichita Symphony, a Magic of Music Orchestra, performance including a cowboy, lariat cow roper, Native American, barbershop quartet and audience participation. Contains 12 color slides and a model release.
  - Publications, 1993; 3; 0.06 Cubic Feet
    - Annual Report Cover, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Knight File Number - 861
      Transparencies and negative of photograph taken for Annual Report Cover, 1993. Color and black & white.